<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Knuth&amp;Stroustrup</string>
    <string name="heading">Donald Knuth</string>
    <string name="heading2">Bjarne Stroustrup</string>
    <string name="imageinfo">Donald Knuth at a lecture</string>
    <string name="imageinfo2">Bjarne Stroustrup in his office</string>
	<string name="desc">Donald Ervin Knuth is an American computer scientist, mathematician, and 
	    Professor Emeritus at Stanford University.
		He is the author of the multi-volume work The Art of Computer Programming.
		Knuth has been called the \"father\" of the analysis of algorithms. 
		He contributed to the development of the rigorous analysis of the computational 
		complexity of algorithms and systematized formal mathematical techniques for it. 
		In the process he also popularized the asymptotic notation. In addition to fundamental 
		contributions in several branches of theoretical computer science, Knuth is the 
		creator of the TeX computer typesetting system, the related METAFONT font 
		definition language and rendering system, and the Computer Modern family of typefaces.
		As a writer and scholar, Knuth created the WEB and CWEB computer programming systems 
		designed to encourage and facilitate literate programming, and designed the 
		MIX/MMIX instruction set architectures.
		
		\n\nKnown for	
		\n*The Art of Computer Programming\n*TEX, METAFONT
		\n*Knuth–Morris–Pratt algorithm
		\n*Knuth–Bendix completion algorithm
		\n*MMIX
		\n*Robinson–Schensted–Knuth correspondence
		
		\n\nNotable awards	
		\n*Turing Award (1974)
		\n*National Medal of Science (1979)
		\n*John von Neumann Medal (1995)
		\n*Harvey Prize (1995)
		\n*Kyoto Prize (1996)
		\n\nText from Wikipedia

	</string>
	<string name="desc2">Bjarne Stroustrup is a Danish computer scientist, most notable for 
	    the creation and development of the widely used C++ programming language. He is currently 
	    Professor and holder of the College of Engineering Chair in Computer Science at Texas A&amp;M 
	    University.		
		Stroustrup began developing C++ in 1978 (then called \"C with Classes\"), and, in his own 
		words, \"invented C++, wrote its early definitions, and produced its first implementation&#8230; chose
		 and formulated the design criteria for C++, designed all its major facilities, and was 
		responsible for the processing of extension proposals in the C++ standards committee.\" 
		Stroustrup also wrote what many consider to be the standard textbook for the language, 
		The C++ Programming Language.
		Stroustrup was the head of AT&amp;T Lab\'s Large-scale Programming Research department, 
		from its creation until late 2002. Stroustrup was elected member of the National Academy 
		of Engineering in 2004. He is a Fellow of the ACM (1994) and an IEEE Fellow. He currently 
		works at Texas A&amp;M University, United States, as a Distinguished Professor where he 
		holds the College of Engineering Endowed Chair in Computer Science.
		
		\n\nNotable awards
		\n*Grace Murray Hopper Award (1993)
		\n*IEEE Computer Society Computer Entrepreneur Award (2004)
		\n*William Procter Prize for Scientific Achievement (2005)
		\n*Dr. Dobb\'s Excellence in Programming award (2008)
		\n\nText from Wikipedia
		
		</string>
</resources>
